Lesson 37.
第37课。
The West Haven Express.
西黑文快车。
punctual: adj. 准时的
We have learned to expect that trains will be punctual.
我们已经学会了期望火车是守时的。
condition: v.   使习惯于, unshakable: adj. 不可动摇的
After years of conditioning, most of us have developed an unshakable faith in railway
经过多年的调理，我们大多数人对铁路发展了不可动摇的信仰
timetables.
时间表。
Ships may be delayed by storms.
船可能会因暴风雨而延迟。
cancel: v.   取消
Flights may be canceled because of bad weather.
由于天气恶劣，可能会取消航班。
But trains must be on time.
但是火车必须准时。
exceptionally: adv. 例外地, dislocate: v.   打乱（计划等）
Only an exceptionally heavy snowfall might temporarily dislocate railway services.
只有一个异常大的降雪可能会暂时脱离铁路服务。
blame: v.   责怪
It is all too easy to blame the railway authorities when something does go wrong.
当出现问题时，很容易责怪铁路当局。
The truth is that when mistakes occur, they are more likely to be ours than theirs.
事实是，当出现错误时，它们比我们的更有可能是我们的。
express: n.   快车；, consult: v.   请教，查阅
After consulting my railway timetable, I noted with satisfaction that there was an express
咨询了我的铁路时间表后，我满意地注意到
train to West Haven.
火车前往西黑文。
direct: adv. 径直地
It went direct from my local station and the journey lasted mere hour and 17 minutes.
它直接从我当地的车站进行，旅程持续了仅17分钟。
When I boarded the train, I could not help noticing that a great many local people got
当我登上火车时，我不禁注意到很多当地人得到了
on as well.
也要。
odd: adj. 奇怪的，异常的
At the time, this did not strike me as odd.
当时，这并没有让我奇怪。
reflect: v.   细想
I reflected that there must be a great many local people besides myself who wished to take.
我反映出，除了我自己外，还必须有很多当地人。
Advantage of this excellent service.
这项出色服务的优势。
Neither was I surprised when the train stopped at widely.
当火车广泛停下来时，我都不感到惊讶。
A tiny station a few miles along the line.
沿线几英里的小型车站。
express: n.   快车；, mighty: adj. 强大的，有力的
Even a mighty express train can be held up by signals.
即使是强大的快车火车也可以通过信号固定。
But when the train dottolled at station after station, I began to wonder.
但是，当火车在车站一个站点旁边散发时，我开始怀疑。
express: n.   快车；
It suddenly dawned on me that this express was not roaring down the line at 90 miles an hour.
我突然意识到，这种快递并没有以每小时90英里的速度咆哮。
chug: v.   咔嚓咔嚓地响
But barely chugging along at 30.
但几乎没有爬行30。
One hour and 17 minutes passed and we had not even covered half the distance.
一小时17分钟过去了，我们甚至没有覆盖一半的距离。
express: n.   快车；
I asked a passenger if this was the West Haven express.
我问乘客是否这是西黑文快车。
But he had not even heard of it.
但是他甚至没有听说过。
lodge: v.   提出, complaint: n.   抱怨
I determined to lodge a complaint as soon as we arrived.
我决心在我们到达后立即提出投诉。
Two hours later, I was talking angrily to the station master at West Haven.
两个小时后，我在西黑文（West Haven）愤怒地与车站大师交谈。
When he denied the train's existence, I borrowed his copy of the timetable.
当他否认火车的存在时，我借用了他的时间表的副本。
triumph: n.   胜利
There was a note of triumph in my voice when I told him that it was there in black and
当我告诉他那是黑色和
white.
白色的。
Glancing at it briefly, he told me to look again.
短暂地瞥了一眼，他告诉我再次看。
asterisk: n.   星号（*）, conduct: v.   引向，引导
A tiny asterisk conducted me to a footnote at the bottom of the page.
一个小的星号将我带到页面底部的脚注。
It said, this service has been suspended.
它说，这项服务已被暂停。